<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Taiwan Tour</string>

    <string name="category_landmarks">Landmarks</string>

    <string name="category_nature">Nature</string>

    <string name="category_food">Food</string>

    <string name="category_activities">Activities</string>

    <string name="nature_qingshui_cliff">Qingshui Cliff</string>
    <!--description from: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Qingshui_Cliff -->
    <string name="nature_qingshui_description">Qingshui Cliff (Chinese: 清水斷崖) is a 21 kilometer length
        of coastal cliffs averaging 800 meters above sea level in Xiulin Township, Hualien County, Taiwan.
        The tallest peak, Qingshui Mountain, rises 2408 meters directly from the Pacific Ocean. The cliff is
        located at the southern part of the Suhua Highway that connects the counties of Yilan and Hualien in
        eastern Taiwan.  It is considered to be a very scenic area and is the highest coastal cliff in Taiwan.</string>
    <string name="nature_elephant_trail">Elephant Mountain (aka Nangang District Hiking Trail)</string>
    <!--description from: https://guidetotaipei.com/visit/elephant-mountain-%E8%B1%A1%E5%B1%B1-xiangshan-->
    <string name="nature_elephant_description">For the best view of Taipei City, make a hike to the top of Elephant Mountain!
        Also known as the Nangang District Hiking Trail and Xiangshan (象山), the hiking trail is located close to the Xinyi Shopping
        District and Taipei 101.  The best time to hike the mountain is during late afternoon, this way you can catch the sunset as well
        as a daytime view and stunning nighttime view of the city, however the trail can get relatively crowded during the weekend.
        The hike takes a total of around 15-20 minutes to the top, and includes lots of stairs! </string>
    <string name="nature_yangmingshan_pational_park">Yangmingshan National Park</string>
    <!--description from: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yangmingshan-->
    <string name="nature_yangminshan_description">Yangmingshan National Park is one of the nine national parks in Taiwan, located between
        Taipei and New Taipei City. The districts that house parts of the park grounds include Taipei\'s Beitou and Shilin Districts; and New
        Taipei\'s Wanli, Jinshan and Sanzhi Districts. The National Park is famous for its cherry blossoms, hot springs, sulfur deposits,
        fumaroles, venomous snakes, and hiking trails, including Taiwan\'s tallest dormant volcano, Seven Star Mountain (1,120 m).</string>
    <string name="food_shilin_night_market">Shilin Night Market</string>
    <!--description from: https://www.smithsonianmag.com/travel/five-must-visit-night-markets-taipei-city-180959342/-->
    <string name="food_shilin_description">Shilin Night Market is Taiwan\'s most famous. The area used to be a trading spot where agricultural
        products were exported to other port cities like Banka or Dadaocheng. Though trading predates the market’s establishment, Shilin has
        been in operation since 1909. It has since become a must-visit munchy destination that brings color and flavor to Taipei\'s nightlife.</string>
    <string name="food_din_tai_fung">Din Tai Fung</string>
    <!--description from: https://www.dintaifung.com.tw/eng/store.php-->
    <string name="food_din_description">Din Tai Fung was founded in Taiwan in 1958, and has grown from a mom-and-pop restaurant into an
        internationally recognized brand. Throughout our journey onto the global culinary stage, we have insisted upon and continue to
        insist upon using natural ingredients, handmade dough, and top quality filling. It is this insistence that has made our xiaolongbao
        world-renowned and allowed us to open branches far and wide, so that we can continue to satisfy taste buds around the world.</string>
    <string name="food_lao_shandong_noodles">Lao Shandong Homemade Noodles</string>
    <!--description from: https://guide.michelin.com/sg/travel/best-taiwanese-beef-noodles-michelin-bib-gourmand-taipei-2018/news-->
    <string name="food_lao_description">One of the most iconic beef noodles shops is Lao Shandong Homemade Noodles, tucked away in the Wan
        Nian Building for nearly 70 years. Deservedly chosen as a Bib Gourmand restaurant this year, Lao Shandong homemade noodles treats
        nothing lightly, from the indulgent broth to handmade noodles to well-cooked beef. This mentality of concentration is what keeps the
        restaurant ahead of the competition after three generations. </string>
    <string name="landmark_taipei_101">Taipei 101</string>
    <!--description from: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Taipei_101-->
    <string name="landmark_taipei_description">The Taipei 101, formerly known as the Taipei World Financial Center – is a landmark supertall
        skyscraper in Xinyi District, Taipei, Taiwan. The building was officially classified as the world\'s tallest in 2004, and remained such
        until the completion of the Burj Khalifa in Dubai in 2010. In 2011, the building was awarded the LEED platinum certification, the highest
        award according to the Leadership in Energy and Environmental Design (LEED) rating system, and became the tallest and largest green building
        in the world.It used to have the fastest elevator in the world, traveling at 60.6 km/h (37.7 mph) and transporting passengers from the 5th to
        89th floor in 37 seconds. In 2016, the title for the fastest elevator was given to the Shanghai Tower in Shanghai.</string>
    <string name="landmark_qinbi_village">Qinbi Village</string>
    <!--description from: https://www.matsu-nsa.gov.tw/User/Attraction-Content.aspx?a=53&l=2-->
    <string name="landmark_qinbi_description">The village of Qinbi is also known as “A Mediterranean town on the Taiwan Straits.” Yet another
        name for the village is Jingao, or “mirror harbor,” derived from the crystal-clear waters of its bordering sea. The present name means
        “rice pile wall,” because from Turtle Island just offshore it resembles a pile of rice against the mountain slope behind it.</string>
    <string name="landmark_jiufen">Jiufen</string>
    <!--description from: https://guidetotaipei.com/visit/jiufen-%E4%B9%9D%E4%BB%BD-->
    <string name="landmark_jiufen_description">Feel spirited away in this decommissioned gold mining mountain town, originally built by the
        Japanese and now a maze of lanes and alleyways with rich history and culture. Founded during the Qing Dynasty, this small town was a
        relatively isolated village until the discovery of gold during the Japanese occupation in 1893, quickly developing the town due to a
        gold rush. Many buildings in the town remain unchanged to this day, reflecting the Japanese influence on both architecture and culture
        on the island. During World War II, the town housed a Japanese prisoner of war camp where captured Allied Force soldiers (mainly British)
        were forced to work in the gold mines. After the war, gold mining activities declined, and the town today exists mainly as a tourist
        destination remembering and celebrating Taiwanese history and culture.</string>
    <string name="activities_new_year">Chinese New Year Lantern Festival</string>
    <!--description from: https://www.iexplore.com/articles/travel-guides/far-east/taiwan/festivals-and-events-->
    <string name="activities_new_year_description">Chinese New Year is a 15 day holiday celebrating the passing of the old year and welcoming in
        the new. It relates to the Chinese Lunar Calendar and begins in February with New Years day and culminates with the Taiwan Lantern
        Festival, a spectacle involving plenty of lanterns, fireworks and food. This period is characterized by lion dances and fireworks and
        it is customary to pay off debts, clean houses, give gifts of money in red envelopes, and have family feasts.</string>
    <string name="activities_dragon_boat">Dragon Boat Festival</string>
    <!--description from: https://www.iexplore.com/articles/travel-guides/far-east/taiwan/festivals-and-events-->
    <string name="activities_dragon_description">The Dragon Boat Festival is a June public holiday originating from China that is celebrated
        on the fifth day of the fifth month of the Chinese lunar calendar. The day is celebrated in Taiwan with dragon boat races, eating
        glutinous rice dumplings, drinking wine and writing spells.</string>
    <string name="activities_moon_festival">Autumn Moon Festival</string>
    <!--description from: https://www.iexplore.com/articles/travel-guides/far-east/taiwan/festivals-and-events-->
    <string name="activities_moon_description">The Moon Festival talks place in late September or early October, on the 15th day of the eighth
        month of the Chinese lunar calendar. The festival celebrates harvest time and is characterized by giving and eating moon cakes. Dragon
        dances, floating lanterns, fireworks and burning incense are also common.</string>
</resources>
